# Technology Entrepreneur, Programmer, Innovator

When I get excited about an idea, there is nothing that can stop me from turning it from a mere idea into a real marketable product. I specialize in startup creation, idea development, and evangelism marketing. I strive to bring innovation to everything that I do and my life goal is to touch the lives of all 7.3 billion people on this earth and change them for the better.



## **Objective**

To continue to follow my passion and love for technology and entrepreneurship and bring innovation into all aspects of my life.



## Experience

#### 2015-present

### **Chief Executive Officer**

Agora Technologies, Troy, New York

www.agoratechnologies.com

- Reinvented the way technology consulting companies are operated
- · Developed an unique zero financial capital startup and zero financial capital maintenance business model
- · National network of team members and clients
- Public launch in summer 2015

### 2013–present

### **Chief Executive Officer**

Flo, New York, New York

- Utilized big data to make retail shopping more efficient
- Created a live "traffic report" of checkout lines in participating stores and provided detailed statistics
- Created proprietary facial detection software



### **Education**

### 2014-2018

## **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science dual Business Management**

Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Troy, New York

Member, RPI Ballroom Dance Team

Member, RPI Jugging and Unicycling Club

Founding Member, RPI Destination Imagination

#### 2010-2014

## **Advanced Regents Diploma**

The Bronx High School of Science, Bronx, New York

Programming and Electronics Department, FRC Team 1155

Student Director of Information Technology, Observatory Yearbook



### Skills

- Entrepreneurship
- Product development
- Marketing
- Programming (C++, C, Java, Python, Objective C, Robot C, MIPS, HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL, JavaScript)
- Responsive front-end web design
- Computer systems construction, repair and maintenance
- Unix/Linux server set up and web hosting
- Adobe proficient(Photoshop, InDesign, Audition, Dreamweaver)
- Photography and videography
- Electronics(microcontrollers, wiring, soldering)
- Mechanical engineering(woodworking, metalworking, construction, and repairs)
- Performer(diabolo, juggling, breakdancing)